Lakshmi Deepak Jarjapu (1) Featured

Senior Consultant seeking assignments in Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Gap Analysis, Solution Architecture, TIBCO BW, TIBCO EMS. Oracle. Unix. MS SQL Server. HTML



Current Designation: Senior Consultant -IT Total Experience: 9 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Prowess Software Services Notice Period: 1 Month

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree: MCA [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad, Mumbai Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Senior Consultant, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Program Management, Project Management, Requirement Gathering, System Analysis, Gap Analysis, Solution Architecture, TIBCO

BW,TIBCO EMS,Oracle,Unix,MS SQL Server,HTML

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Over 9+ years of experience in TIBCO.

Experience in designing, development of Applications using TIBCO Active Enterprise suite of products. Excellent interpersonal skills, ability to work well with others, in both supervisory and development staff roles.

Experience in development of business logic and automated business processes using TIBCO Business Works.

Excellent communication and interpersonal skills and good team player.

Has gone through the complete phase of software development life cycle (SDLC), Agile Methodology including analysis, program design, coding, debugging, testing, documentation, installation and maintenance process framework. Well at operating independently as well as in team environment. Strong written and oral communication skills, self-motivation, creativity and ability to adapt to new technologies and applications.

Trained new team members to impart them product and module specific knowledge.

Work Experience

Prowess Software Services as Senior Consultant -IT Oct 2019 to Till Date

Having decent 9years of experience in TIBCO(8 years in TIBCO BW and 1 year in TIBCO STREAMBASE). My role in current project as Team Lead. Follow Agile Methodology. We use to interact with client in daily basis in scrum call.

Reliance Industries Limited as Senior Consultant Apr 2015 to Sep 2019

Synechron Technologies as Junior Software Engineer Dec 2011 to Feb 2015

Education

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from Andhra University in 2005

PG: MCA (Computers) from Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University (JNTU) in 2008

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
TIBCO BW 5.11, TIBCO EMS 8.4.0	
TIBCO SAP Adapter 7.0,	
Windows, Unix, Linux	
HTML	
Oracle 10g, MS-SQL Server 10.0	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time